{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943968273","data":{"timestamp":" 946943968273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" a0506dde-57f0-4629-8d63-95385fc4e660"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943986888","data":{"timestamp":" 946943986888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943990914","data":{"timestamp":" 946943990914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943995589","data":{"timestamp":" 946943995588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944000381","data":{"timestamp":" 946944000381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944005209","data":{"timestamp":" 946944005209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944011407","data":{"timestamp":" 946944011407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944015418","data":{"timestamp":" 946944015418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944019335","data":{"timestamp":" 946944019335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944022954","data":{"timestamp":" 946944022953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944026377","data":{"timestamp":" 946944026376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944030558","data":{"timestamp":" 946944030558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944041491","data":{"timestamp":" 946944041491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944049280","data":{"timestamp":" 946944049280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944055221","data":{"timestamp":" 946944055221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944059044","data":{"timestamp":" 946944059044"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944062689","data":{"timestamp":" 946944062689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944068681","data":{"timestamp":" 946944068681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944072879","data":{"timestamp":" 946944072879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944077264","data":{"timestamp":" 946944077264"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944082161","data":{"timestamp":" 946944082160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944085781","data":{"timestamp":" 946944085781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944093903","data":{"timestamp":" 946944093903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944097401","data":{"timestamp":" 946944097401"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944100586","data":{"timestamp":" 946944100586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944104170","data":{"timestamp":" 946944104170"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944108803","data":{"timestamp":" 946944108802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944112353","data":{"timestamp":" 946944112353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944115479","data":{"timestamp":" 946944115479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944121274","data":{"timestamp":" 946944121269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944138869","data":{"timestamp":" 946944138869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 291c3944-60a2-48e4-82d5-303dda275a5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944156954","data":{"timestamp":" 946944156954"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 1bb6c44f-edcf-4764-9f1a-0898eea55d93"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944160830","data":{"timestamp":" 946944160830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 1bb6c44f-edcf-4764-9f1a-0898eea55d93"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944160879","data":{"timestamp":" 946944160879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 1bb6c44f-edcf-4764-9f1a-0898eea55d93"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944180155","data":{"timestamp":" 946944180154"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3f52b5c-7bcd-4fd7-a78b-d61aa02ceeab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944184175","data":{"timestamp":" 946944184175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3f52b5c-7bcd-4fd7-a78b-d61aa02ceeab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944189813","data":{"timestamp":" 946944189813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3f52b5c-7bcd-4fd7-a78b-d61aa02ceeab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944193500","data":{"timestamp":" 946944193500"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3f52b5c-7bcd-4fd7-a78b-d61aa02ceeab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944202179","data":{"timestamp":" 946944202179"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3f52b5c-7bcd-4fd7-a78b-d61aa02ceeab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944205621","data":{"timestamp":" 946944205620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3f52b5c-7bcd-4fd7-a78b-d61aa02ceeab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944211677","data":{"timestamp":" 946944211677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3f52b5c-7bcd-4fd7-a78b-d61aa02ceeab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944215279","data":{"timestamp":" 946944215278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3f52b5c-7bcd-4fd7-a78b-d61aa02ceeab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944216213","data":{"timestamp":" 946944216213"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3f52b5c-7bcd-4fd7-a78b-d61aa02ceeab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944234333","data":{"timestamp":" 946944234333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944240933","data":{"timestamp":" 946944240932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944247004","data":{"timestamp":" 946944247004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944250717","data":{"timestamp":" 946944250716"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944257241","data":{"timestamp":" 946944257241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944263524","data":{"timestamp":" 946944263524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944267374","data":{"timestamp":" 946944267374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944272137","data":{"timestamp":" 946944272136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944276088","data":{"timestamp":" 946944276088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944281275","data":{"timestamp":" 946944281275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944289335","data":{"timestamp":" 946944289335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944294793","data":{"timestamp":" 946944294793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944298993","data":{"timestamp":" 946944298993"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944302511","data":{"timestamp":" 946944302511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944306046","data":{"timestamp":" 946944306046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944309836","data":{"timestamp":" 946944309836"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944313891","data":{"timestamp":" 946944313891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944318107","data":{"timestamp":" 946944318107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944321779","data":{"timestamp":" 946944321779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944329653","data":{"timestamp":" 946944329653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944334352","data":{"timestamp":" 946944334352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944338279","data":{"timestamp":" 946944338279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944341814","data":{"timestamp":" 946944341814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944346534","data":{"timestamp":" 946944346534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944349754","data":{"timestamp":" 946944349754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944352982","data":{"timestamp":" 946944352981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944358750","data":{"timestamp":" 946944358749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 818b057b-3632-4315-9aa5-beab3607a479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944379691","data":{"timestamp":" 946944379690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944380075","data":{"timestamp":" 946944380075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944380571","data":{"timestamp":" 946944380571"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944380926","data":{"timestamp":" 946944380926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944381342","data":{"timestamp":" 946944381342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944381830","data":{"timestamp":" 946944381830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944382066","data":{"timestamp":" 946944382065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944385294","data":{"timestamp":" 946944385293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944385331","data":{"timestamp":" 946944385331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944386058","data":{"timestamp":" 946944386057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944386466","data":{"timestamp":" 946944386465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944386771","data":{"timestamp":" 946944386771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944386998","data":{"timestamp":" 946944386997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944387204","data":{"timestamp":" 946944387203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944387528","data":{"timestamp":" 946944387528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944387764","data":{"timestamp":" 946944387763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944390949","data":{"timestamp":" 946944390949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944391364","data":{"timestamp":" 946944391363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944393950","data":{"timestamp":" 946944393950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944394163","data":{"timestamp":" 946944394162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944394375","data":{"timestamp":" 946944394374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944397880","data":{"timestamp":" 946944397880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944401633","data":{"timestamp":" 946944401632"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944402656","data":{"timestamp":" 946944402656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944405288","data":{"timestamp":" 946944405288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944405661","data":{"timestamp":" 946944405661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944406144","data":{"timestamp":" 946944406144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944406487","data":{"timestamp":" 946944406487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944406891","data":{"timestamp":" 946944406890"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944407364","data":{"timestamp":" 946944407364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944407599","data":{"timestamp":" 946944407598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944410830","data":{"timestamp":" 946944410829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944410870","data":{"timestamp":" 946944410869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944411594","data":{"timestamp":" 946944411594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944411996","data":{"timestamp":" 946944411996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944412302","data":{"timestamp":" 946944412301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944412519","data":{"timestamp":" 946944412518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944412728","data":{"timestamp":" 946944412728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944413055","data":{"timestamp":" 946944413055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944413294","data":{"timestamp":" 946944413293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944415921","data":{"timestamp":" 946944415919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944416041","data":{"timestamp":" 946944416041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 0486b739-52ac-4f26-a152-7fcf8e202ccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944436151","data":{"timestamp":" 946944436150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 57919264-16e7-4fbd-80d3-ad5099836646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944442815","data":{"timestamp":" 946944442814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 57919264-16e7-4fbd-80d3-ad5099836646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944444415","data":{"timestamp":" 946944444414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 57919264-16e7-4fbd-80d3-ad5099836646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" faraja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARAJA"," userResponse":" FARAJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944447420","data":{"timestamp":" 946944447419"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 57919264-16e7-4fbd-80d3-ad5099836646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" faraja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARAJA"," userResponse":" FARAJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944449035","data":{"timestamp":" 946944449034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 57919264-16e7-4fbd-80d3-ad5099836646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" familia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944452807","data":{"timestamp":" 946944452806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 57919264-16e7-4fbd-80d3-ad5099836646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" familia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944454426","data":{"timestamp":" 946944454425"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 57919264-16e7-4fbd-80d3-ad5099836646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fupi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" FUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944459200","data":{"timestamp":" 946944459199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 57919264-16e7-4fbd-80d3-ad5099836646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fupi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944460817","data":{"timestamp":" 946944460816"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 57919264-16e7-4fbd-80d3-ad5099836646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944465666","data":{"timestamp":" 946944465666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 57919264-16e7-4fbd-80d3-ad5099836646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944467293","data":{"timestamp":" 946944467293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 57919264-16e7-4fbd-80d3-ad5099836646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" farasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" FARASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944470410","data":{"timestamp":" 946944470409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 57919264-16e7-4fbd-80d3-ad5099836646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" farasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" FARASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944471996","data":{"timestamp":" 946944471996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 57919264-16e7-4fbd-80d3-ad5099836646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" funzo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUNZO"," userResponse":" FUNZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944476327","data":{"timestamp":" 946944476326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 57919264-16e7-4fbd-80d3-ad5099836646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" funzo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUNZO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944477937","data":{"timestamp":" 946944477936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 57919264-16e7-4fbd-80d3-ad5099836646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fulana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANA"," userResponse":" FULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944482272","data":{"timestamp":" 946944482271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 57919264-16e7-4fbd-80d3-ad5099836646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fulana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANA"," userResponse":" FULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944484297","data":{"timestamp":" 946944484295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 57919264-16e7-4fbd-80d3-ad5099836646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" fulana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944484411","data":{"timestamp":" 946944484411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 57919264-16e7-4fbd-80d3-ad5099836646"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fulana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANA"," userResponse":" FULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944499429","data":{"timestamp":" 946944499428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3dcc8ef-2553-456f-add7-7af24ba3f23e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944504792","data":{"timestamp":" 946944504790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3dcc8ef-2553-456f-add7-7af24ba3f23e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944506378","data":{"timestamp":" 946944506378"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3dcc8ef-2553-456f-add7-7af24ba3f23e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" faraja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARAJA"," userResponse":" FARAJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944509168","data":{"timestamp":" 946944509167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3dcc8ef-2553-456f-add7-7af24ba3f23e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" faraja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARAJA"," userResponse":" FARAJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944510766","data":{"timestamp":" 946944510765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3dcc8ef-2553-456f-add7-7af24ba3f23e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" familia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944518882","data":{"timestamp":" 946944518881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3dcc8ef-2553-456f-add7-7af24ba3f23e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" familia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" START_FAMILIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944530811","data":{"timestamp":" 946944530811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3dcc8ef-2553-456f-add7-7af24ba3f23e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" familia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944532438","data":{"timestamp":" 946944532438"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3dcc8ef-2553-456f-add7-7af24ba3f23e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fupi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" FUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944537146","data":{"timestamp":" 946944537145"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3dcc8ef-2553-456f-add7-7af24ba3f23e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fupi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944538745","data":{"timestamp":" 946944538744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3dcc8ef-2553-456f-add7-7af24ba3f23e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944543295","data":{"timestamp":" 946944543294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3dcc8ef-2553-456f-add7-7af24ba3f23e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944544908","data":{"timestamp":" 946944544907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3dcc8ef-2553-456f-add7-7af24ba3f23e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" farasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" FARASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944548276","data":{"timestamp":" 946944548275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3dcc8ef-2553-456f-add7-7af24ba3f23e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" farasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" FARASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944549891","data":{"timestamp":" 946944549890"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3dcc8ef-2553-456f-add7-7af24ba3f23e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" funzo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUNZO"," userResponse":" FUNZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944552495","data":{"timestamp":" 946944552494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3dcc8ef-2553-456f-add7-7af24ba3f23e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" funzo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUNZO"," userResponse":" FUNZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944554079","data":{"timestamp":" 946944554078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3dcc8ef-2553-456f-add7-7af24ba3f23e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fulana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANA"," userResponse":" FULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944556963","data":{"timestamp":" 946944556963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3dcc8ef-2553-456f-add7-7af24ba3f23e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fulana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANA"," userResponse":" FULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944558990","data":{"timestamp":" 946944558988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3dcc8ef-2553-456f-add7-7af24ba3f23e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" fulana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944559071","data":{"timestamp":" 946944559071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" b3dcc8ef-2553-456f-add7-7af24ba3f23e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fulana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANA"," userResponse":" FULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944578931","data":{"timestamp":" 946944578931"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 8bf74fbc-0461-43e9-8379-8f106f2a1c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_k-f-s"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944583115","data":{"timestamp":" 946944583115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 8bf74fbc-0461-43e9-8379-8f106f2a1c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_p-n-f"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944587180","data":{"timestamp":" 946944587180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 8bf74fbc-0461-43e9-8379-8f106f2a1c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-u-f"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944590879","data":{"timestamp":" 946944590879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 8bf74fbc-0461-43e9-8379-8f106f2a1c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-j-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944594442","data":{"timestamp":" 946944594442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 8bf74fbc-0461-43e9-8379-8f106f2a1c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-n-b"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944597545","data":{"timestamp":" 946944597545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 8bf74fbc-0461-43e9-8379-8f106f2a1c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-z-g"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944601362","data":{"timestamp":" 946944601362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 8bf74fbc-0461-43e9-8379-8f106f2a1c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_n-f-b"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944605530","data":{"timestamp":" 946944605530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 8bf74fbc-0461-43e9-8379-8f106f2a1c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_l-f-o"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944608984","data":{"timestamp":" 946944608983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 8bf74fbc-0461-43e9-8379-8f106f2a1c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_y-f-k"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944612427","data":{"timestamp":" 946944612427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 8bf74fbc-0461-43e9-8379-8f106f2a1c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_p-s-f"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944618214","data":{"timestamp":" 946944618213"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 8bf74fbc-0461-43e9-8379-8f106f2a1c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_f_p-s-f"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944632854","data":{"timestamp":" 946944632854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" e772b3fe-e1f3-47ae-b1d2-648c0e0ccd13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944717051","data":{"timestamp":" 946944717048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" e772b3fe-e1f3-47ae-b1d2-648c0e0ccd13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944717192","data":{"timestamp":" 946944717192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" e772b3fe-e1f3-47ae-b1d2-648c0e0ccd13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944756614","data":{"timestamp":" 946944756612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" e772b3fe-e1f3-47ae-b1d2-648c0e0ccd13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944776809","data":{"timestamp":" 946944776809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" ab23630e-883f-41a7-b8ca-f603bc10744f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-l-ch"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944780564","data":{"timestamp":" 946944780564"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" ab23630e-883f-41a7-b8ca-f603bc10744f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_k-f-l"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944785905","data":{"timestamp":" 946944785905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" ab23630e-883f-41a7-b8ca-f603bc10744f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_s-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944788508","data":{"timestamp":" 946944788507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" ab23630e-883f-41a7-b8ca-f603bc10744f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_f_s-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944820626","data":{"timestamp":" 946944820626"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" dbed6a07-6a88-4972-bede-891a46b6c6d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_i_y"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944828135","data":{"timestamp":" 946944828135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" dbed6a07-6a88-4972-bede-891a46b6c6d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_i_y"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944834821","data":{"timestamp":" 946944834820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" dbed6a07-6a88-4972-bede-891a46b6c6d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_v_a_f"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944842437","data":{"timestamp":" 946944842437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" dbed6a07-6a88-4972-bede-891a46b6c6d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_v_a_f"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944849042","data":{"timestamp":" 946944849041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" dbed6a07-6a88-4972-bede-891a46b6c6d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_u_z"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944855644","data":{"timestamp":" 946944855643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" dbed6a07-6a88-4972-bede-891a46b6c6d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_f_u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944862286","data":{"timestamp":" 946944862285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" dbed6a07-6a88-4972-bede-891a46b6c6d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_i_v"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944868920","data":{"timestamp":" 946944868919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" dbed6a07-6a88-4972-bede-891a46b6c6d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_p_s"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944876370","data":{"timestamp":" 946944876369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" dbed6a07-6a88-4972-bede-891a46b6c6d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_p_s"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944883031","data":{"timestamp":" 946944883031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" dbed6a07-6a88-4972-bede-891a46b6c6d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_z_f"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944889651","data":{"timestamp":" 946944889651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" dbed6a07-6a88-4972-bede-891a46b6c6d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_g_f"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944896261","data":{"timestamp":" 946944896261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" dbed6a07-6a88-4972-bede-891a46b6c6d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_z_f_n"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944902901","data":{"timestamp":" 946944902901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" dbed6a07-6a88-4972-bede-891a46b6c6d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_r_d"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944910754","data":{"timestamp":" 946944910754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" dbed6a07-6a88-4972-bede-891a46b6c6d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_f_r_d"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944934993","data":{"timestamp":" 946944934992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 252d4fef-8036-4640-9391-f0055e0088e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_i_y"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944941675","data":{"timestamp":" 946944941675"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 252d4fef-8036-4640-9391-f0055e0088e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_v_a_f"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944948339","data":{"timestamp":" 946944948338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 252d4fef-8036-4640-9391-f0055e0088e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_u_z"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944955005","data":{"timestamp":" 946944955005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 252d4fef-8036-4640-9391-f0055e0088e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_f_u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944961654","data":{"timestamp":" 946944961653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 252d4fef-8036-4640-9391-f0055e0088e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_i_v"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944969128","data":{"timestamp":" 946944969127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 252d4fef-8036-4640-9391-f0055e0088e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_i_v"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944975805","data":{"timestamp":" 946944975804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 252d4fef-8036-4640-9391-f0055e0088e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_p_s"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944982473","data":{"timestamp":" 946944982473"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 252d4fef-8036-4640-9391-f0055e0088e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_z_f"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944989130","data":{"timestamp":" 946944989129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 252d4fef-8036-4640-9391-f0055e0088e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_g_f"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946944995827","data":{"timestamp":" 946944995827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 252d4fef-8036-4640-9391-f0055e0088e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_z_f_n"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945002437","data":{"timestamp":" 946945002436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 252d4fef-8036-4640-9391-f0055e0088e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_r_d"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:F..F.all.10.rand.say.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946945014480","data":{"timestamp":" 946945014479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_025914"," gameId":" 252d4fef-8036-4640-9391-f0055e0088e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_F..F.all.10.rand.say.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_f_r_d"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}